[Music]
today's video I'm taking a look at
manual life insurance this is tribal
insurance and the reason why we
particularly get this one is because the
one that we get is for multiple trips or
else I think there's a lot more options
for you guys if you're just going to get
the one time but if you're thinking that
you're going to travel maybe during the
winter and maybe summer to the US or
maybe during the winter to two places or
more then I would get a multiple thing
it's just a little bit cheaper that way
anyways so this is the website I'm going
to zoom in on the link up here so it's
manif travel. CA once you're there you
put in traveling
Canadians then I would choose this
multiple trip emergency medical you can
get all the inclusive you can see the
two different ones by yourselves and I
also want to highlight if you just want
to get a single one you can go ahead and
get it from here however if you're just
looking into a single trip I would look
into every option out there but for
multiple trips this is I think one of
the best ones just because they have
that option not all insurance companies
have that option for some reason so I'm
going to click on here the first one
then if you scroll down you're going to
see what this covers so this is a
multi-rip plan and it does cover you for
the entire year so that's the good thing
that's what I like about this it's not
just the onetime thing but anyways let's
just scroll down you guys going to see
more information then click on get a
code on your left 10 side from here
we're going to choose multiple trips it
could be single as well departure date
departure date doesn't have to be exact
so if you're thinking of a date just
make sure it's earlier than what you
think so maybe you're thinking maybe for
January the 31st I would start it on the
30th or even earlier if you're not 100%
sure about the date that said I'm going
to choose the 26 then trip duration it's
about 7 Days however most of our trips
are 14 days so 18 days would be good
then you have to choose your Province
we're going to choose Ontario in this
case what type of coverage I would
suggest looking for family if you guys
have a family you're going with your so
choose family if you have kids choose
companion if you just have your wife
going with you or your partner or single
just for you this case we choose family
going to scroll down now keep in mind
that sadly you can't really create an
account and if you want to um extend
this out later on so once the year's
over you can just sign up for it again
just like by doing a click you have to
fill up everything again which is odd
and hopefully they fix that later on but
yeah you have to apply for it again
anyways we're just going to click here
on the left hand side how many Travelers
including yourself so that's three in
total in my case cuz I just have the one
kid then we just have to fill out the
birthday of the primary traveler so
that'll be you that signing up then go
ahead with your spouse and keep going
with your kids and then how many are
dependent children depends on their age
usually you just put one or however many
kids you have number of parents or
grandparents this case it's us too then
we can go on and just click on show
plans all right so from here you guys
can go on and just mess around with a
few things if you don't want any
deductibles just choose zero if you want
some deductible then go ahead the price
should go down on you and the higher the
deductible the price should be lower so
let's say you guys have to go up to
10,000 which at that point
I don't know if even you want a health
plan but it does depend and if you want
zero that would be one the most
expensive to me between Zer and 500
there isn't a huge price difference so I
just go for zero trip duration that does
change things too so if you going just
for a week then this will be
significantly lower if you're going for
18 days or so this will be higher for us
it's an average of 14 days so we're just
going to go on with that we can go on
and click on select and you guys can
also view the plan details so if you
click here it's going to tell you
exactly what's this all about and you
can learn more about it just by clicking
on the PDF as well again this is what's
selected then just scroll down a little
bit and click on the left hand side
you're going to see a box keep going
down all the way down on the left hand
side go ahead and press apply once you
do so you have to fill up all the
information for everybody so get ready
to fill up a lot of information so go on
fill up everybody's first names second
names last names and all the information
that here required after you've done so
scroll all the way down and on the left
hand side you guys can click on continue
all right so afterwards just review
everybody's information and just keep
scrolling down it's going to tell you
exactly how much this is going to cost
you and just keep scrolling down until
you see this amount and then put in your
credit card you're going to see the back
of your credit card that number three
digits put it there and once you put in
all that information scroll the way down
just put a check mark on I have read and
accepted terms and conditions click on
purchase on the the left hand side from
here you're going to be just done with
everything it's going to say thank you
and then print on the left hand side
make sure to print it out well you don't
really need to print it out as long as
you press print and then save it on your
phone you take a screenshot you can also
just copy over the PDF the most
important thing will be your policy
number so you should see PDF here plus
your policy number that's the most
important thing about this and if you
scroll all the way down you're going to
see starting new application and you are
done return home so right not check your
email make sure to keep that PDF with
you and you're all done if you guys have
any questions comments you guys can
write down comments area don't forget to
subscribe and like thank
[Music]
you